<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>André Mendes</title>
    <link>https://mendesc.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on André Mendes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:08:13 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mendesc.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leetcoding a palindomer checker</title>
      <link>https://mendesc.com/posts/leetcoding-a-palindomer-checker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:08:13 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendesc.com/posts/leetcoding-a-palindomer-checker/</guid>
      <description>I find leetcoding enjoyable even outside interviewing context. Not enough to take it as a hobby tough.
As now I search for a role, I practice it in my spare time (aha).
My favourite platforms are exercism.io, leetcode.com and hackerrank.com.
On leetcode.com you got to compare your successfull results to other submissions and this is really cool. Good data visualisation is always nice!
I find it very noteworthy how a fancy and expressive one-line solution does not hold a good position against others regarding performance and memory usage:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacex Challenge</title>
      <link>https://mendesc.com/posts/spacex-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 23:04:53 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendesc.com/posts/spacex-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Spacex Challenge This is a Full-stack challenge I wrote for a company. I am still waiting for a response from them.
In sumary, they asked to use SpaceX’s graphQL API to exhibit SpaceX data.
I built it with Next.js and I am not a Full-stack developer. Next.js is cool.
I thought the resulted looked fine so I&amp;rsquo;m sharing: https://spacex-launches-nine.vercel.app/
Source: https://github.com/dremendes/spacex-launches</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About my 2022</title>
      <link>https://mendesc.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:27:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendesc.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>I got laid off last December. The whole team, actually. I thought it would be easier to get a new job but I was wrong. The market right now if full of excellent engineers looking for a new role.
Companies with open roles are overwhelmed with applications, they are taking longer to answer than ever before.
Even companies without financial insecurities are laying people off. They are using this seasonal situation to rub down on costs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>